GODZILLA 70TH
ANNIVERSARY PRODUCTION
ODO ISLAND NAVY DETACHMENT
- Let's go!
- Heave ho!
Engine normal.
Roger.
- Fuel-system checks out.
- Roger.
Ensign Shikishima?
Tsukuba Naval Air Corps,
Tachibana. Remember me?
Of course. I am
greatly in your debt.
I'm amazed you were able to
land that bucket of bolts...
on this Swiss
cheese of a runway.
You haven't lost your touch.
In simulated dogfights, no, but
suddenly, I'm a real kamikaze pilot.
Then be grateful
for the downtime.
But it's odd.
We've scoured your rig and
can't find anything wrong.
What are you implying?
I'm on your side. We need
more people like you.
Why obey an order to "die honorably"
when the outcome is already clear?
- Get the guns!
- Yes, sir!
- An enemy raid?
- I don't know!
- What is it?
- Something big!
A new Yankee weapon?
Taki! Taki!
- Light the beach!
- Roger!
Taki!
What in the hell?
It's Godzilla.
- What?
- A local told me.
It brings up deep-sea fish.
G-G-Godzilla?
We're screwed. Take cover!
Take cover!
What the hell is it?
Nobody knows.
- Ensign Shikishima.
- Sir.
Can you reach your 20mm gun?
You're our only gunner.
We're just mechanics.
But what if it just
makes it angry?
A 20mm gun can kill anything!
Hurry before it gets too close.
Go! Now!
Go.
Hurry.
What's he doing?
Now! Fire!
It's coming this way.
- What do we do, sir?
- Ammo!
Fetch the ammo!
You idiot! Don't shoot!
Cease fire!
Cease firing!
Fall back! Fall back!
Retreat!
Mr. Tachibana!
I'll draw it this
way. Shoot to kill!
You guys didn't deserve this.
Hey!
Everybody's dead!
They're all dead...
because you didn't shoot!
Damn it!
You.
Hey!
Watch where you're
stepping, man.
Is that you, Koichi?
Sumiko!
How is this possible?
Weren't you a kamikaze pilot?
You have the nerve
to show your face?
You're a disgrace!
Look what happened because
of cowards like you!
If you'd all done your duty...
my children wouldn't have died.
Do you know if my
parents survived?
Everybody's dead.
This whole place was
engulfed in flames.
Your folks too.
My children met the same fate.
MY DEAREST SON, KOICHI...
"Come back alive," right?
That's what you said.
Stop, thief!
Out of my way!
- Move!
- Grab that woman!
- Please!
- What?
Get back here!
What?
Hey!
Finally. Where did you go?
It's your fault for
sitting out in the open.
I would have been seen.
You've been here the whole time?
Yeah, waiting for you
to get up and move.
I bet you're hungry.
Why didn't you just abandon her?
Hey!
And leave her in
a place like that?
No?
Interesting.
Please don't follow me.
Are you going to leave
us to die on the street?
I don't care.
After you're done,
you're leaving.
Hear that? He's
so mean and scary.
Where's your husband?
Is he a soldier?
Do I look like I'd
have a husband?
What?
Whose kid is she?
- Does it matter?
- Of course, it does!
During the air raids...
her dying mother begged me.
So you...
have no relation to that child?
Nope. So what?
What are you, stupid?
You're in no state
to care for a baby.
You couldn't leave her either.
Name?
AKIKO
No, I meant you.
Noriko.
Why do you dress like
a vagrant? By choice?
Well, I'm no harlot.
Don't look insulted.
You've got to survive
somehow. Who could blame you?
What about family?
HARU SHIKISHIMA -
EIICHIRO SHIKISHIMA
Your parents?
Yeah.
They were killed
in the air raids.
Then you and I are the same.
What?
No, you can't...
stay...
Hey!
What's the story?
- What do you mean?
- Don't play dumb.
The mother and
child you picked up.
Think you're some kind of saint?
No.
They just showed up.
If they're staying,
you picked them up.
It's a bit late
to play the hero.
Count me out. I'm done caring.
Wait.
Is that girl able to breastfeed?
No. She's not the
child's mother.
What?
At this rate, she'll
die of malnutrition.
Right?
So you found a child, but you
have no idea how to care for it.
What were you thinking?
I don't know.
It's not for you.
Adults can survive on anything.
Use it to make rice gruel.
Well...
there goes my prized white rice.
What a nuisance, I swear.
Damn it. I'm soaking wet.
Was there any work?
Well, I did find something.
What's the matter?
The money's not bad either.
Look. They even paid an
advance of 3,000 yen.
That's wonderful!
It must be a scam, like the rice
you carried that got stolen.
It's nothing like that.
What makes you so sure?
It's government approved.
There's a reason
why it pays well.
Like what?
During the war, both sides laid
thousands of mines in the sea.
This is a cleanup job.
But the pay is extremely
good because, well...
it comes with a
certain amount of risk.
What are you, crazy?
You just survived a war!
What else can I do?
At this rate, we'll starve.
Akiko's life depends on it.
I understand that but...
This brings in money.
With money, we can even
buy American powdered milk!
For that, I'd do...
I forbid you to die!
Don't worry. Just because it's
dangerous doesn't mean I'll die.
It's not like being
a kamikaze pilot.
And besides...
I'll be on a special
boat made to evade mines.
This is specially made?
Hey, are you our
new sharpshooter?
I'm Shikishima.
Sailor?
Fighter pilot.
What? This guy's useless.
You're an ex-airman?
Just a military
castoff. Worthless.
Disappointed?
When seeing this boat?
The US and Imperial navies laid
60,000 mines off Japan's coasts,
all kinds, but the worst are
the American magnetic mines.
Any approaching boat made
of metal sets them off.
Ah, hence the wood.
The boy catches on fast.
We mostly handle moored mines.
But wood boats are the
best countermeasure.
I'm Noda.
I developed naval
weapons during the war.
Boat captain Akitsu
and Mizushima.
"The Kid" and "Doc".
I'm not fond of that nickname.
And I'm not a "kid".
You're still green,
so "Kid" it is.
I know. I wasn't in the war.
This is a mine sweeper, the Shinseimaru.
It's paired with the Kaishinmaru.
The mines rise up from the
seabed like balloons on strings.
Between our two boats is
a cable with a cutter.
All we do is clip the mine wire,
and it floats to the surface.
Then we fire on it with
this baby, rat-tat-tat-tat.
Take a look.
This one's a bit tricky.
May I give it a try?
Are you sure?
You have to estimate its position
and account for movement.
Woo-hoo!
Nice shot!
Same with fighter planes.
Not that I saw any real action.
What?
You didn't? That makes
me and Shikishima equals.
Hardly. You can't fly a plane.
If I'd gone to war,
I would've learned.
If only it had lasted longer.
You'd better not mean that.
No, sorry.
You fool.
Fire! Fire! Fall back!
You all right?
Another bad dream?
A dream.
Right.
I was dreaming.
Or maybe...
you're just a dream.
- What's wrong with you?
- Tell me.
This is Japan, right?
I really did return
alive, right?
- I returned alive!
- Stop!
Yes, I know.
I know.
Nice place you built here.
Worth every penny saved.
SHIKISHIMA
Drink?
Oh, why, thank you.
May I take a photo?
- Please don't waste your film.
- That smile!
Hold it. Hold it.
Ready?
- Thank you.
- Hey, Doc.
No coveting now.
Of course not. Noriko's
a married woman.
Please stop.
I'm not a wife.
What does that mean?
She just moved in on her own.
She had no place to
go, so I let her stay.
And the child?
She brought her too.
But they aren't related.
Akiko was orphaned
in the air raids.
- Wow, that's a beautiful story.
- No.
It just sort of happened.
Daddy.
- Akiko.
- What?
I told you. I'm not your father.
Shikishima.
- Don't say that.
- That's truly harmful.
Fate has brought you
together as a family.
Accept it. Embrace it.
Make them happy!
Enough!
I don't want that.
Why not?
Welcome home. I just
returned myself.
What are you wearing?
How does it look?
I got a desk job in Ginza.
But don't I give
you enough money?
It's time I stood
on my own two feet.
At this rate, you'll
never find a wife.
Have you seen how fast
Ginza is rebuilding?
This is so sudden.
Not for me, it isn't.
What about Akiko?
What will you do with Akiko
while you are away at work?
Sumiko has promised
to look after her.
She was very excited, boasting
she'd raised three kids already.
In that case, I
suppose it's all right.
Thanks. I'll go get Akiko now.
The colossal sea creature
is projected on a course
to reach the Japanese
archipelago within a few weeks.
General Douglas MacArthur
stated with regret
that recent Soviet movements
prevent US military assistance
but called upon Japan
to begin strengthening
its security forces.
What did this?
A giant shark?
Or a whale?
No shark or whale could do that.
A new Soviet weapon?
That's not weapon damage.
Then what could it be?
- An enormous creature.
- Like what?
Just admit you have no clue.
I was skeptical
until I saw this.
Godzilla.
Look there!
Floating deep-sea fish.
Just like on Odo Island.
What did you see there?
It was like a prehistoric
dinosaur-turned-monster.
The local inhabitants
called it "Godzilla."
Godzilla?
Nonsense. You were half
asleep and saw an enemy tank.
Whether you believe me or
not, something wiped out...
the entire garrison on Odo.
Hold on.
I thought the
Americans did that.
Odo was never targeted by
US island-hopping forces.
It was a repair base
for kamikaze planes.
Does that mean...
you were a kamikaze pilot?
If this is the same
Godzilla I saw...
it must have grown much
larger and more powerful.
Hold on a second.
Why were we called out
here to begin with?
They don't expect us to
fight that in this boat!
Yes, they do.
We obviously don't
stand a chance!
That's a US warship! What
can we do in this little rig?
Stall for time.
Stall?
The Takao is coming
from Singapore.
The heavy cruiser?
Rather than scuttle it,
it's being returned.
That's good news!
The Takao's a beast!
So we've been ordered
to stall for time.
Why can't the US handle
it? It's their ship.
They're worried
about the Soviets.
Any military maneuvers
would raise alarms.
They'd prefer we
handle the small stuff.
This isn't small stuff, and
all we've got is a 13mm gun.
I was told to make use
of recovered mines.
Ah, now I see! This is why
they called us out here.
Plus, our main weapon has
to be locally scavenged?
We're also not allowed to
talk about it with anyone.
There it is. Their
favorite gag order.
This country never changes.
Perhaps, it can't.
Take a breather.
Thank you.
Don't push yourself too hard.
I can't help it.
This is Godzilla.
I hear you. When I start
remembering the war...
I can't sleep sometimes.
I have to avenge them.
But at the same time...
I'm terrified of that thing.
We'll need more than
a pair of those.
What is it?
There are way more of these
fish than I saw off Odo.
Sound the alarm!
Godzilla's coming!
So it's coming, huh?
Hey, Kid! Prepare
to drop the mines!
- Roger!
- Man the gun!
We can't fight it on this!
- We can still flee!
- Agreed.
- Doc, stand aft and report!
- Captain!
Kaishinmaru, do you copy?
Get ready to land a big one!
We're taking all the
credit for victory.
- You idiot.
- Captain!
If we run, the Takao
will never catch up,
and the monster
will head for Tokyo.
I don't want to see
it in flames again.
But this boat is
no match for it!
I thought you hated
government orders.
With a passion.
But you know what?
Somebody's got to do it.
Okay, never mind!
Doc, the engine!
I'm working on it!
Shikishima!
Hurry! Over here!
- Captain!
- I know!
- Full throttle!
- Right!
Drop the mines!
We'll never make it!
We gotta try something!
Now, Kid!
Here goes!
Did we get it?
No, we did not!
Bad, bad, bad...
Shikishima, the gun!
Roger!
Shikishima!
Completely ineffective!
The mouth! What
about in the mouth?
Reel! Reel!
Drop it!
Mizushima, now!
Right!
What? No.
No!
Get down!
Did we get it?
No!
The Takao!
They made it!
Oh, no.
Is it down?
What's that?
You're finally awake.
Where am I?
A Yokosuka hospital. We
were transported here.
What of the Kaishinmaru
and the Takao?
Godzilla.
What happened to it?
Whereabouts unknown.
It was headed for Tokyo. We need
to sound the evacuation order.
The government is not
telling the public.
Why? We must hurry!
To prevent mayhem and confusion.
Are you kidding me? We need
to begin evacuating now!
No one will take
responsibility...
for the chaos.
Information control
is Japan's specialty.
Tell me what happened.
It's got nothing to do with you.
What is it that
torments you so badly?
You took me in, saved me, and
we've been together since.
But you won't let me into
any part of your life.
If you're carrying
some burden...
I wish you'd share it with me.
I'm...
someone...
who fled his duty...
as a kamikaze pilot.
What?
On the day of my sortie...
I pretended my
plane was faulty...
and made a detour...
landing on Odo Island.
These are photos...
belonging to the
mechanics there.
They all perished.
That night...
a dinosaur-like
monster came ashore.
I was asked...
to shoot it with the
gun on my fighter.
But I froze up...
and ran again.
When I came to the next day...
I found them all dead. People
longing to see their families!
The monster...
was called Godzilla.
The other day, it reappeared.
And once again...
I couldn't do anything.
I'm someone...
who wasn't supposed to live.
Listen to me.
Everyone who survived
the war is meant to live.
- How do you know?
- I just do!
As flames took my parents,
they ordered me to live.
So whatever happens next,
I know I must survive!
That has kept me going.
I can't.
They beckon to me in
my dreams every night.
"Hurry and come," they say.
"Why are you still
cheating death?"
It's just a dream, just
ghosts you created.
Maybe it's an illusion.
What if I'm actually
dead already?
I died long ago
on that island...
and lie rotting.
You and Akiko are just the
last dream of a dead man.
That must be it! It has to be!
You are alive!
You are alive, Koichi.
Can't you feel it?
Okay, hold the spoon.
Gently.
- Grip it firmly.
- Okay.
Good, now stir the broth.
You're doing great!
- There, it's done!
- Yeah!
I added your favorite, radish.
- Radish!
- Taste it for me.
- Okay.
- Are you ready?
First the soup, then radish.
Can I...
put this all to rest?
I'd like to try to live again.
Is that what I think it is?
Hurry and report it.
Hurry!
Yes, sir!
Patrols report the creature is
heading east toward Tokyo Bay.
Is it close then?
- What is it?
- I don't believe it.
Is it here?
Is that really a living thing?
This is Tokyo Bay Defense, requesting
permission to detonate Zone 4!
It's almost here.
Entering Zone 4!
- Now!
- Detonate!
Status?
No good.
It had no effect!
Blockade breached! It's
heading to Shinagawa!
And it is gargantuan!
Oops.
Thank you.
This is an emergency
news report!
A giant sea creature has
come ashore near Ginza.
Those near Ginza, follow police
instructions and evacuate.
- This is not a hoax.
- Ginza!
Are you hurt? You okay?
What's going on?
What just happened?
Is that... Godzilla?
It's a scene that defies belief.
A giant creature on the loose,
trampling Ginza underfoot!
Tearing whole buildings apart!
The Nippon Theater,
beloved icon of the people,
is crumbling before
our very eyes!
The Ginza survived air
raids but not this!
This monster has
turned it to rubble!
And now the monster
is coming this way!
I can see its enormous head
passing in front of us!
It's dangerously close!
Move!
Get up!
- Koichi!
- Do you want to live? Come on!
Did they get it?
This is...
the same as before.
Noriko.
Noriko!
Nori...
Damage wreaked by
the giant creature
includes some 30,000
killed and injured
and 20,000 homes and
buildings destroyed.
Recovery operations are underway,
but the path the creature took
carries a risk of radiation
that is impeding progress.
Police have cordoned off central Ginza
to collect shards of the creature
which are of unknown composition
and potentially hazardous.
I'm so sorry.
What now for Akiko?
We pull together, that's what.
Hey, Akiko.
You like playing with me when
Dad's away at work, right?
Where's Mommy?
Mommy had to go away for
a little while for work.
But you'll have
me with you, okay?
You can't forgive
me. Is that it?
It's my fault...
for thinking I
could dream again.
Mr. Shikishima.
There's actually a strategy being
hatched to defeat Godzilla...
led by private citizens.
It lacks any real basis
for viability, but...
will you take part?
SPECIAL DISASTER
COUNTERMEASURE HEARING
- Wait, everyone here is...
- Yes.
- Ex-navy personnel.
- You're informed.
Really?
I'm Captain Hotta, formerly
of the Yukikaze Destroyer.
As you all know,
Tokyo again faces...
an unprecedented crisis.
This time, a monster attack.
But we have no defense apparatus
of our own to protect our people.
What's more, any GHQ-led military
action runs the risk of escalating
US-Soviet tensions.
In short, we must confront the monster
with our strengths as private citizens.
This is why we've
gathered you here.
But we've negotiated the
use of four destroyers
originally slated for
handover to the UN.
Are you saying...
you want us back on navy ships?
I saw what it did in Ginza.
There's no way to defeat it.
Especially from boats
that have been disarmed.
You're dreaming!
That's what I'm here to
explain if you'll allow.
Mr. Noda?
The plan...
Pardon me.
The plan was drafted by me, Kenji
Noda, ex-Navy technical officer.
The first thing to know
is that this creature the people
of Odo Island call "Godzilla"
cannot be hurt by
conventional weaponry.
I saw it take heavy artillery
fire from the guns of the Takao
and quickly heal itself.
Quiet, please.
So we need a totally
different approach.
Let me give you a demonstration.
This is ocean salinity water.
This wood model is weighted down
just enough to barely float.
What happens if we pipe in freon
gas, enveloping it in bubbles?
That's easy. Bubbles or
not, it would stay afloat.
That's what you'd think.
It sinks!
The freon bubbles prevent the
model from contacting the seawater.
My idea is to entrap Godzilla like
this and sink it to the ocean floor.
Did you have any idea
Doc was such a bigwig?
No.
At over 1,500 meters in depth,
the Sagami Trench is the
deepest place in nearby waters.
The plan is to strap freon cylinders
to Godzilla and let them foam.
We'll create a bubble membrane.
It'll sink so rapidly that
the pressure will crush it.
We'll kill it with
the power of the sea.
That's the outline for
Operation Wada Tsumi.
It's of the sea. Won't it
withstand the pressure?
After 25 seconds, every square meter
will apply 1,500 tons of pressure.
Even ocean-born creatures cannot
bear such rapid pressure changes.
Can you promise...
that would kill Godzilla?
Godzilla is an unknown organism.
We can only predict
what will happen.
But this is our
best alternative.
Will it kill it? Or will it not?
I can't absolutely guarantee it.
Shikishima!
It can be done!
Mr. Shikishima.
Hear me out, please.
Now, let's get to the details.
Two ships will corral
Godzilla and wrap it in cable.
The cable will have multiple freon
gas cylinders attached to it.
The gas will be released
as it's being tied.
And Godzilla will take a
rapid plunge of 1,500 meters.
What if that fails?
There is a Plan B.
Look into the courtyard.
Inflate!
I'm Itagaki of Toyo Balloon.
What you just saw
is an inflatable flotation
device like the kind...
used in navy aircraft.
CO2 is shot into air sacs for
buoyancy, like a life preserver.
When Godzilla hits the bottom, we
raise it right back to the surface.
We quickly raise it
back up to the surface.
If it can bear the pressure, it'll then
contend with massive decompression.
I can't say for sure
that it wouldn't survive.
But we must do what we can.
You've all survived
a tragic war.
So it pains me to ask you again
to put your lives on the line.
But understand this.
We can't rely on the US
or Japanese governments.
So the future of this
country is in our hands.
I can't do it.
I have a family.
And that goes for
most people here.
Why are we always the ones
drawing the short straw?
We got enough of
that in the war.
Please.
I beg you to listen
very carefully.
This is not an order. You're
all free to leave if you wish.
We have no right to stop you.
This plan...
does it mean certain death?
Of course not.
Then it definitely
beats wartime.
It can't be helped.
Someone has to do it.
Who can sail the
ships if not us?
- Yeah.
- That's right.
Well, then! Are we in, boys?
My friends...
thank you.
Hear, hear!
What a surprise, to find you're the
mastermind of such a grand plan.
Well, I've had a direct
encounter with it.
So the task fell to me.
And we were called
for the same reason.
Do you think
Godzilla will return?
I think we can
assume that Godzilla
has added Tokyo to
"its territory".
I expect it'll be back within
ten days at the latest.
That soon?
You set up
radiation-detecting buoys?
Visual detection isn't enough.
How can you expect it to
walk right into your trap?
- I can't.
- What, no plan?
Who do you think I am?
Of course, I have a plan.
We have acoustic minesweepers.
We use the speakers to play a
recording of Godzilla's voice.
- Its voice?
- Yeah.
It'll see it as another
territorial competitor.
- Hopefully.
- Hopefully?
You don't instill confidence.
And that flotation device?
I can't envision
that working well.
Any other ideas then?
I know! We pull it up
with the destroyers.
Godzilla weighs some 20,000 tons,
too heavy for two destroyers.
Oh.
In short, your plan
is full of holes.
If you have a better
one, let's hear it.
Mr. Noda.
Can you get ahold
of a fighter plane?
Fighter plane?
I could anger it with gunfire
and draw it to Sagami Bay.
All planes were decommissioned.
Even if you could,
it shoots a heat ray.
You'd risk your life
flying so close.
I'll take that risk.
A fighter plane is
nimbler than a boat.
You're not aiming to
get shot down, are you?
Do you have a death wish?
You're drunk.
You just want to avenge Noriko.
Got a problem with that?
It's too late.
You should've
married her before!
You knew how she felt.
Don't you think I
wanted that too?
Then why didn't you?
Because...
my war isn't over yet.
- You found a plane?
- Yes.
But it's a unique one.
The short-range interceptor
Shinden was built at war's end.
It was designed to
shoot down bombers.
And reach speeds
of over 400 knots.
Its canard design and four
30-mm guns pack a punch.
It's a plane full
of innovations.
Only a few prototypes
were field deployed.
They were kept here for a
mainland battle that never came.
They were left to rust
and are in bad shape.
It's not airworthy as is.
What we need is a top mechanic,
someone who knows their
way around a fighter plane.
I know just the person.
Ex-Odo Island
detachment mechanic?
- Sosaku Tachibana?
- Yes.
Tachibana.
No known current address.
- I see.
- We're swamped with search requests.
This will take time.
I need to locate him urgently.
There's not much more I can do.
- I beg you, please!
- What?
The country's future
depends on it!
I'm sure, but I can't
do the impossible.
Sorry.
Well then...
where was he posted
before Odo Island?
I've asked everywhere.
But this Tachibana probably
doesn't want to be found.
We can find another mechanic.
Any other leads?
Just wait a bit longer.
Why must it be him?
- Godzilla can come at any time.
- It has to be Tachibana!
He's going to get my message.
Please!
Tachibana.
Mr. Tachibana! It's really you!
What's this about?
Wait.
The Odo Island massacre
was all my fault?!
Are you serious?
I'm sorry.
I knew if I angered
you, you'd come find me.
How dare you!
The Ginza attack...
was the same as Odo.
It was Godzilla.
I need you to repair
a fighter for me,
so I can kill it!
I needed to find you,
to ask for your help.
That's why I wrote
those letters.
Please forgive me!
You're on your own.
I'm not helping you.
No, wait, Mr. Tachibana!
Please listen to me! I need
your help to kill Godzilla.
It's something only you can do.
I exploded a mine in its mouth, and
that hurt it more than a ship's guns.
It's vulnerable from
the inside. You get me?
You don't mean...
I can kill it if I fly a plane
full of explosives into its mouth.
Kamikaze...
The war isn't over...
for you either.
- You got that injury by falling down?
- Ow.
It's swelling up
like a grapefruit.
It's embarrassing,
but I was drunk.
I barely remember it.
I guess you deserved to celebrate
after finding Mr. Tachibana.
A canard, huh?
I'd heard rumors, but
they actually did it.
Mr. Tachibana.
Thank you all for coming!
You're Mr. Tachibana?
So this is the phantom
short-range interceptor Shinden?
Can you make this fly?
We'll do all we can.
Thank you.
Good luck. Good luck.
What's wrong?
Brighten up, Mastermind.
It's bad for morale.
I know it's my plan.
But I'm feeling we'll need
a miracle to make it work.
Doing nothing won't
cause a miracle either.
You're right.
Take a look at
these guys' faces.
They're not stupid.
They know they're
risking their lives.
And yet...
their faces are beaming.
They're happy. This time,
they'll make a difference.
Make a difference.
We all came through war.
This time, we're
making it right.
2F CONFERENCE ROOM 3, SPECIAL
DISASTER COUNTERMEASURE HQ
Hurry up!
Make room.
One hour ago, east
of Hachijo Island,
33.10 North, 140.01 East,
we got Geiger readings
from multiple buoys
followed by...
here and here.
Godzilla's coming.
At last.
At this rate, it's due to
arrive over the Sagami Trench
at 1100 hours
tomorrow, which means
we have to mobilize and
be in positions by 0800.
But tell me...
will your device
be ready by then?
Take us with you.
The final three hours
will be critical.
We want it to be perfect.
But you could get
caught in the fight.
We've all seen war too.
Then everybody, go home tonight.
Spend the time with your families.
You mean... be prepared?
Come to think of it...
this country has treated
life far too cheaply.
Poorly armored tanks,
poor supply chains resulting in half of
all deaths from starvation and disease,
fighter planes built
without ejection seats,
and finally, kamikaze
and suicide attacks.
That's why this time...
I'd take pride in a
citizen-led effort...
that sacrifices no lives at all!
This next battle...
is not one waged to the death...
but a battle to
live for the future.
Let's do it!
Finally, tomorrow's the day.
I can't wait.
You're not going.
What do you mean?
Well, you're useless
with that arm, anyway.
Even Shikishima's going!
Because I'm not a veteran?
I can be useful.
Not having been to war...
is something to be proud of.
I want to defend my country too.
Take me with you!
We've been a team
for a long time!
I'm begging you!
Take me with you!
I want to go with you!
We leave you the future.
Captain!
Mr. Noda!
A little lower.
Careful.
Here you go, Akiko.
I want to...
thank you for everything.
Akiko.
Did you have fun with Auntie?
It was fun.
Good. I'm glad.
Is that for me?
Thank you.
- Akiko?
- Hmm?
Is this you, me and Mom?
That's Mom there.
I see.
It's really good.
Why do you look sad?
What's wrong?
Akiko.
There, there.
It'll be all right.
I'm not leaving you.
Mr. Tachibana.
Is it ready?
Give me a minute.
The bomb you ordered.
Two machine guns, 140kg...
120 rounds, 80kg...
and one main fuel
tank, 400kg, removed.
Instead, a No. 25 bomb in the
nose and a No. 50 in the fuselage.
Now, I can finally
pay them back.
That's funny.
Part of me wants to live.
Same as all the men that day.
They all wanted to go home.
But instead, they got
squashed like bugs.
I understand.
This was drawn by
a girl named Akiko.
I want to protect her future.
I will stop Godzilla
no matter what.
You're finally ready.
Then, this is important.
Look here.
The bombs' safety.
Pull it right before flying in.
Got it?
One more thing.
Akiko.
Are you all by yourself?
Look.
TO SUMIKO...
LOOK AFTER AKIKO. USE
THIS MONEY FOR HER.
From Daddy?
Huh? Yeah, from Daddy.
It's all right. Don't worry.
This is Kuroshio 12,
35.03 North, 139.41 East.
Many deep-sea fish found!
Godzilla sighted in Sagami Bay!
Underwater guidance
decoy activated!
Take only essentials with you!
Hurry and get aboard!
Let's get a move on.
Mizushima took our advice?
It's the best thing for him.
I didn't want Shikishima
to fly either.
A failed kamikaze
pilot? It worries me.
He's got Akiko. He'll
make it back alive.
Underwater decoy team destroyed!
Godzilla has entered Sagami Bay!
Wada Tsumi ships, leave port now!
Look.
There!
It's already here?
Godzilla's through the final
defense line! Heading for shore!
I'm off!
Time to end it once and
for all, Shikishima.
Leave port now! Repeat. Wada
Tsumi ships, leave port now!
What now? The plan's ruined!
We set sail anyway.
We need to sink it over Sagami
Trench, or it won't work.
Shikishima will have to lure it!
Move out!
Let's go!
Radio from Mr. Shikishima!
I'm in the air, preparing to
lure Godzilla to the target area.
We'll be ready.
Get there quickly.
Don't do anything rash! I won't
forgive you if you orphan Akiko.
You hear me, Shikishima?
He's ignoring me.
Telegram!
Coming.
Yes?
Mrs. Shikishima?
- Telegram.
- Thanks.
Wow, he's luring it out to sea!
Godzilla looks
really ticked off.
It's in pursuit.
Our turn now.
All ships, battle positions!
Freon, ready!
46-cm shells, ready!
Flotation switch, ready!
Cables, ready!
All circuits, ready!
Power on, release safety device!
That's it. Keep coming.
- Team 1, attack as planned.
- As planned!
Attaboy.
That's Godzilla's heat ray.
The ships won't survive this.
All ships must evacuate!
No, this is okay.
Stick to the plan.
But the heat ray!
Once fired, it takes
time to regenerate.
We go, now!
Give the order!
Commence Operation Wada Tsumi!
Deploy 46-cm shells, freon
cylinders, and flotation device!
Shikishima!
Crane deployed!
Roger!
Maintain course, Hibiki!
Hibiki, maintain course!
Maintain speed. Some
damage inevitable.
Hibiki closing in, 4 meters!
2 meters!
- Brace for impact!
- Crossing complete! Full speed!
- Full speed!
Yes! Yes!
- Captain, the switch!
- Roger!
Oh, no. Not yet?
Almost.
Ready...
Hit it, Captain!
- Freon!
- Got it!
Depth 1,200 meters!
1,300 meters!
- 1,400 meters!
- Keep going!
- Dive!
- 1,450 meters!
1,500! Target-depth exceeded!
We sunk Godzilla!
Did it succeed?
Persistent bastard.
- Move to Plan B.
- Do it.
Now rise!
Depth 1,200 meters! 1,100
meters, 1,000 meters!
Cables stopped!
They stopped at 803 meters!
Why? Why did they stop?
It chewed through them.
Hibiki, we'll pull Godzilla up!
90 degrees, max speed!
The two ships lack the thrust.
We've no choice.
Give it all you can!
Yes, sir!
At this rate,
the crane won't hold.
Clear out!
This is Yokohama
Eisen's Fujimaru!
Doing our best to help!
That voice.
Mizushima here. Is
that you, Captain?
Kid, is that you?
You bet!
This is Toyo Kisen's
Koeimaru, here to help!
And Yokohama Eisen's
Nikkomaru! At your service!
Shiokazemaru, assisting!
Tetsuyumaru.
- Nanamimaru.
- Minamimaru.
- Kisshomaru.
- Junseimaru.
- Wakamaru.
- Heimitsumaru.
Tenyumaru.
- Kaiomaru.
- Hyuga.
- Choukamaru.
- Shoseimaru.
- Taramaru.
- Yasakamaru.
The useless to the rescue!
I'll be damned.
I gotta admit I'm
glad to see him.
All you tugboats out there!
Let's catch a Godzilla!
- Everybody, pull!
Godzilla's rising again!
Come on, show your face!
Depth 700 meters!
Keep coming, keep coming!
It's not damaged enough!
All ships, evasive action!
What's he doing?
No.
- Don't!
- Stop!
Shikishima!
Shikishima...
No, look!
I see him.
I see him!
Pilot ejected! He's alive!
This seat has an
ejection device.
Just pull that lever.
Live.
Mr. Tachibana.
Shikishima!
You did it!
Kid!
Sumiko!
Koichi!
- Koichi.
- Akiko.
What?
Is your war...
finally over?
Yes.
RYUNOSUKE KAMIKI
MINAMI HAMABE
YUKI YAMADA
MIOU TANAKA, YUYA ENDO
KISUKE IIDA, SAE NAGATANI
HIDETAKA YOSHIOKA
MUNETAKA AOKI
SAKURA ANDO
KURANOSUKE SASAKI
IN MEMORY OF SHUJI
ABE (19492023)
WRITTEN, DIRECTED AND
VFX BY TAKASHI YAMAZAKI
Subtitle translation
by: Anthony Kimm