TRANSGRESSIVE PRODUCTION
PRESENTS
A FILM BY QUARXX
Holy shit, I made it.
I'm not hurt.
- Did you see the state of your car?
- Huh?
Did you see the state of your car?
I can't believe how lucky I was.
Did you take a look at my bike?
You were on that bike?
Yes, that was me.
I'm really sorry.
I didn't see you.
I tried to avoid you at the last second.
The car must have rolled over, I think.
Are you alright?
Considering the violence
of the impact, you were...
You were also really lucky.
Are you hurt somewhere?
I'm gonna call 911.
Shit, I must have left it in the car.
After the accident...
...do you remember
getting out of the car?
Uh, no, I...
No.
I must have had a shock.
I remember my head banging
against the dashboard.
Does your head hurt?
Do you have a wound?
No.
What's your name?
Nathan.
Daniel.
Nice to meet you, Nathan.
Nice to meet you, Daniel.
It's a surprising meeting,
don't you think?
Right.
We'll remember it for sure.
You are my first undead.
What?
We didn't make it.
Don't you understand?
- What are you talking about?
- You heard me.
I heard you, but it makes no sense.
You must be in shock.
No, but I'm no longer in denial.
I've been here longer than you.
I must have died on the spot.
It must have taken you a little longer.
It also took me a little while
to understand.
What are you saying?
What about all this?
What's all this?
You can say whatever you want,
but this moment is real.
This is my body.
My feelings.
The last thing I remember
is sliding into the crash barrier
and being sad at the idea
of not seeing my wife again.
I have good news.
You'll see her again.
Then I remember a huge, powerful,
black mass crashing into me.
It was you and your car, Nathan.
You're crazy.
It should be easy to get
to the bottom of it, right?
Yes, it should.
Well?
Wait, the driver's compartment
is completely staved in.
And that doesn't ring a bell?
Shut up!
What you're telling me
is not possible.
What did I tell you?
No, no. No.
No, no, no, no!
No, no, no!
No! No, no, no!
Calm down, Nathan.
What do you mean, calm down?
You didn't come face to face
with your own corpse!
I can't be looking my best
under your car either.
But I...
I feel alive.
I...
I feel...
I feel sad, I feel scared.
That's human feelings!
It might be just a phase.
What do I know?
It's the first time
it's happened to me.
But I don't want to die.
It's not possible.
My wife will be very sad.
It will kill her.
She warned me
not to buy this motorbike.
What about me?
My friends? My kids?
I'm only 45!
I had my life ahead of me.
We always think
we have our life ahead of us
until it ends.
Thank you
for the condescending lesson,
but it doesn't help.
No, no, I refuse.
Funny, you didn't mention your wife.
What?
Won't you miss your wife?
Why do you say that?
Because I will miss mine a lot.
Mind your own business, please.
Do you realize the implications?
Life after death exists!
Here we are, talking normally
as if nothing has happened.
To think I was a non-believer!
If only I'd known!
I feel good, despite the circumstances.
I feel a sense of fulfillment.
I don't give a shit
about your fulfillment!
I want my body back!
I want my life back!
I'm dreaming.
It's the effect of the anesthetic.
I must be in surgery by now.
I must be on the operating table.
I'm gonna wake up from this nightmare.
Really?
You don't exist!
What are you doing?
No, no, no. Don't!
No.
- I said don't!
- Quiet.
You need to face reality,
Nathan!
This doesn't feel right.
I don't like it at all.
Could you please turn my head around?
Wait.
Is that better?
A little better.
How did you manage to drag my body
out of the car if you're dead?
I don't know, I just did.
I don't know how this works yet.
A car is coming.
He might help us.
What are you talking about?
Please call 911.
I've had an accident.
I fell into the ditch.
Call for an ambulance.
Hurry up!
- He can't hear us. We're dead.
- Yeah, but...
Maybe I can be revived.
I'm gonna rejoin my body.
I'm getting the hell out of here!
Call an...
Call an ambulance, goddammit!
I don't believe it.
The bastard's picking my pockets!
Hey!
I can't believe this.
I'm a fucking ghost.
Am I really dead?
If there was any doubt before,
there is none now.
It's a catastrophe.
There's no way back.
It's a disaster.
A total disaster.
Is it true what they say
about life after death?
Heaven, hell, all that.
We should find out anytime now.
Are we gonna be judged
based on our actions?
You know that song,
We're All Going to Heaven?
Even if we've killed someone?
You've killed someone?
No, no.
Not really, but kind of, yes.
- Who?
- My wife.
- Your wife?
- Yes, but it's not what you think.
Shh!
What?
Do you hear that?
No. What?
The music.
What?
What music? I don't hear any music!
Why don't I hear it?
Listen!
I hear nothing except silence.
A deadly silence.
I don't like your sense of humor.
That must be for us.
The music, it's coming from there.
Why don't I hear it?
It's magnificent!
What's magnificent?
I've never heard music like it.
Fuck. Why don't I hear it?
It is the way into the next world.
Let's not waste any more time!
Not so fast!
Who is this one for?
How should I know?
Actually, I do hear your music now.
But, it's not really music.
It's more like screams.
No it's not,
it's harps and trumpets.
We don't hear the same thing at all.
We each have our own door.
There's no way
I'm going through that door.
Have you seen it?
Would you go through it?
I would hesitate, it's true.
There you go, then.
But if you hear things
coming from that door that I don't hear,
and I hear music that you don't hear
coming from the other one,
I think the message is clear!
That's easy for you to say!
I didn't kill my wife!
What exactly do you mean?
Hey! I have the right to explain myself.
I have the right to defend myself!
She was sick!
You know that very well!
I only put her out of her misery!
Murder is murder, Nathan.
You're starting to piss me off!
You have your place in heaven!
Give me a break!
I'm leaving you.
I'm going back to my door.
They must have anticipated
this possibility.
I had to try.
You don't behave
like a good dead man, Nathan.
And what is a good dead man,
Mr. Perfect?
A dead man who accepts past actions
and present consequences.
After all, you don't know
what's behind that door.
Looking at it, it doesn't
make me want to be curious.
Fuck you and your lessons in morality!
You shouldn't talk to me this way.
You've already run me over.
You owe me an apology.
OK, I'm sorry.
But I didn't see you.
Right.
No hard feelings.
To tell you the truth,
I wasn't paying attention either.
I was distracted by a little girl
playing at the side of the road.
What do we say at times like this?
Godspeed?
Not funny.
Good luck, then.
It's not working.
I don't understand.
Well, well...
Mr. Moralizer...
...any dirty little secrets
you haven't shared?
I don't understand.
I can't hear the music anymore.
Where are my parents?
No.
Are you the man on the motorcycle
who ran into me?
What? I don't think so.
Are you the little girl who was playing
at the side of the road?
I got lost,
I'm looking for my mom.
- This can't be happening.
- What did you do?
I don't know, I thought I avoided her.
Everything is alright.
I'm sorry.
It was a friend's birthday,
I had a few drinks.
You killed an innocent child.
You're a fine one to talk!
My situation was different!
- It was for her own good!
- For her own good?
Her own good earned you
a pretty nice life insurance payout!
- How do you know that?
- The dead know everything!
Why... Why is he saying that?
What's your name, darling?
Alice.
That's a beautiful name.
That's it!
Now I can hear
those damned screams, too!
I'm screwed.
I'm going to hell, too.
Stop with your whining!
I'm trying to make amends
for your stupidity here.
Sweetheart.
You're gonna come with me.
We're gonna go to a beautiful place,
and everything's gonna be alright. Come.
I can't go with people I don't know,
and I don't know you.
It's true that you don't know me,
but we won't go very far.
We...
We're just gonna walk through that door.
Can you hear the music?
- Yes.
- I'd never done anything wrong before.
This is not fair!
It was an accident.
It's murder and you know it.
You were drunk!
Come with me. We'll follow the music
and go through that door.
You'll see, on the other side
you'll be reunited
with your dad, your mom,
your sister, your cat, everyone.
Come!
Calm down, sweetheart.
Calm down.
Why are you screaming?
I'm not going to eat you.
You're both going to hell
for what you've done to me!
I had nothing to do with this.
I'm a victim, just like you.
That's enough!
No! No! No!
That was radical.
What? We'd had enough, no?
So what now?
What do you mean?
You think we have a choice?
Not really.
After you.
You go first.
Can you hear the screams now?
Drop it.
If you'd let me go through the other door
when I heard the music,
I wouldn't be here.
- I'm sorry.
- Yeah, right.
It's really sadistic, making us
go through of our own accord.
- Don't you think?
- Yes.
I would have preferred
to be forced to enter.
Yes, well...
No!
She wanted to die. She...
She was depressed.
She hated her life!
Ask her.
All I did was help her
get what she wanted.
I don't deserve to rot in hell!
Right.
I get it.
You preach forgiveness
and redemption
but the slightest mistake
gets us the cane!
It's the same old story.
Do as I say and not as I do.
Well, I'm not going!
I don't want to.
Well?
OK, OK. I'm going.
We can't go on like this!
We need help!
We need protection!
She needs us!
Do you hear me?
She needs us.
You're not thinking straight!
You're her father
and you're scared of her!
You have no balls.
You're a coward!
Are you blind?
I won't let her down,
do you understand?
I won't let her down either.
She needs help!
Fight for your daughter!
You can help her!
I spend my life doing that!
You wish she didn't exist,
so you could leave!
You never considered her
to be your daughter!
You should be ashamed,
saying that to me!
I only ever have
her best interests at heart.
You think she's happy?
For God's sake,
she's only nine years old!
You're good for nothing!
She just needs your help
after what's happened, and love!
She's not like other girls.
When will you see it?
You're meant to be her father
and you're afraid of her!
How are you doing, Jeanne?
We need to talk, OK?
Can you tell me
what happened yesterday?
I found baby birds.
I wanted to feed them.
And that's what you did?
Yes.
I gave them crumbs from my cookies.
What happened next, Jeanne?
The mother bird returned to the nest.
She was flying around me.
Was she afraid for her babies?
Yes.
What then, Jeanne?
Then,
I took them in my hands
and strangled them.
It was easy.
Have you ever poked people with pens?
Who?
My little sister.
Why were you hurting your sister?
Because I hate her and she's stupid.
Who else did you want to hurt?
Dad and Mom.
Were they scared of you?
Yes.
Have you ever hurt them?
When?
At night, when they were asleep.
After that,
they locked me in my room.
What you did to your sister
is very wrong.
Do you realize that?
Can you tell me
what you did to her?
Jeanne?
Can you tell me?
Breakfast!
Breakfast! Breakfast! Breakfast!
Tony?
Tony, where are you?
Come on!
I know what you did.
You don't have to hide.
I made you strawberry toast,
the way you like it.
Come out!
Come out or I'll lock you up
and throw away the key
and no one will come to feed you.
Come on.
What did you do?
Nothing.
Yes, you did!
What about Dad and Mom?
It wasn't me.
Who was it, then?
There's only you, Claire, and me here.
How are we going to manage now?
I don't know.
You should have thought
about that before.
Come on, sit down.
Thank you.
But it wasn't me.
Stop saying that!
What's my name?
Not now.
Yes, now.
Tony. Tony the Monster.
Yes.
Yes!
Tony the Monster.
I like it when you say my name.
There's no point hiding
in the magic cave anymore.
Really?
Yes, silly!
They can't see you anymore.
I'll be allowed upstairs?
For real?
Are you deaf? I just told you!
And don't pretend it's the first time.
You had to go upstairs to kill them.
I'm not stupid.
I'm happy to be able to go upstairs.
Thank you.
Well, come on.
You know I'm a little girl, right?
And a little girl needs
her dad and her mom.
I know.
Well, in the meantime
they are dead.
You're a real pain in the ass!
It's wonderful!
Is the weather nice?
I don't know.
But this is no time for sunbathing.
I've never seen the sun.
That can wait.
First you must wash.
You stink!
Come with me.
Undress yourself.
Now...
...I can do whatever I want.
If I want to be a princess, I can.
If I want, I can do this.
What should I do now?
Get in there.
And now what should I do?
Is it always gonna be like this?
"What should I do?
Should I do this? Should I do that?"
It's boring!
I don't know what to do.
I've never done this before.
You turn on the taps.
It's wonderful.
You got it now?
It's amazing.
Take some soap and scrub yourself.
I never want to come out again.
You have to.
We need to tidy up the house.
You didn't hold back.
I told you, it wasn't me.
Not that again!
What's that?
It's grenadine.
Can I have a sip?
No.
Please.
You're so annoying.
I don't like it.
Good!
We can't leave them like this.
What do we do?
We need to tidy up.
Tidy what up?
Them.
We can't leave them there.
We have to put them somewhere.
Where should we put them?
I don't know. I'm thinking.
We could put them under the bed?
Yes, that's not a bad idea.
You take Mom and I'll take care of Dad.
I can't lift him. He's too heavy.
I'll bring him later.
Wait.
We can't just tidy them away like that.
First, we're gonna give them a surprise.
What kind of surprise?
Do you know what happened to me?
This morning I woke up
and went downstairs as usual
to get my breakfast.
I come to the table.
I wait and I wait
and nobody comes to serve me.
Absolutely nobody!
They leave me to starve to death.
Do you know
why I had nothing but cereal?
No! Tell us! Tell us!
Because my parents were dead!
Right!
They were lying in a pool of blood,
full of holes.
I didn't understand,
because I knew I hadn't killed them.
Although I did have a moment of doubt.
So I carried out an investigation.
And do you know what I found?
No.
Do you know?
No, we don't!
I found this!
Yeah, a big, fat monster
was hiding in my cellar,
and he killed my dad and my mom.
Tell them you killed them,
ugly, fat monster!
Tell them!
I don't remember.
You do remember!
You're just scared of being punished.
No.
I have no recollection of my life
before you picked me up
in the magic cave.
I don't remember having ever existed.
You're talking nonsense.
Do you know the punishment
for big fat lying monsters?
What about you? Do you know?
We hang them! To the scaffold!
Exactly!
Climb up on that.
What's my name?
Tony the Monster.
Any last words
before your execution?
I am Tony the Monster.
And I'm innocent!
Say, I'm getting hungry.
When do we eat?
Do you know how to cook?
Uh... no.
Neither do I.
Except for toast.
I like toast.
Put her down
and push her under the bed.
Alright.
Do you want me to go get Dad?
Yes, please.
Will you wait for me?
- Yes.
- OK. I'll be going then.
I am a princess
I can do whatever I want
And what do I do now?
You do as we say.
You put him under the bed.
I'm beautiful, don't you think?
Yes, you are.
I'm lucky to be so beautiful.
All the girls in my class want to be me.
They are all so jealous.
Why can't I see myself?
Because it's best
if you don't see yourself, Tony.
It's better this way.
Wait!
Wait for me.
What do we do now?
I don't know. Shall we leave?
Yes, we should go somewhere,
but where?
I don't know anywhere.
My aunt lives on a farm
300km from here.
She might help us.
Is 300km far away?
I don't know.
But I think so.
Who is it?
- I don't know.
- You want me to go?
No, stay here.
Yes, what is it?
Is your mummy in?
No, she's not here.
Is your daddy in?
No, he's not here either.
Right.
I have a delivery for Mrs. Jacobs.
That's your mom, right?
Yes.
Could you fetch the person
who takes care of you?
Please.
I'm all alone at the moment.
Aren't you too young to be left alone?
Well, I'm not really alone, I'm with Tony.
Tony? Alright.
Tony it is, then.
Can you call him, please?
I don't think it's a good idea.
Of course it's a good idea.
I have this package to deliver.
And I need an adult to sign for it.
Do you understand?
Are you sure?
You don't want your mom to have
to collect it from the depot, do you?
Call Tony, sweetheart.
Alright. Tony?
Tony?
Tony!
This may be a gift for you.
Listen, young lady,
isn't it time you changed your clothes
and washed your hands?
You are covered in I don't know what.
It's strawberry jam. Tony!
Look, I have work to do.
Here is the missed-delivery card.
Tony!
And the address of the depot.
Tony?
Tony!
Tony? Tony!
Stop hiding. It's not funny.
Tony!
Tony, this isn't funny!
Tony?
Tony!
Where are you? Tony!
Don't look at me! Go away!
Stop it!
Claire.
Why isn't Mom coming?
Because she's dead.
Did you kill her?
Tony killed her.
Is he going to kill me, too?
Yes.
Can I please finish my drawing first?
No.
Tony is hungry.
You'll be fine in there.
Get in there.
You won't feel a thing.
Fire department
The house is burning
The house has burned down
It was not me who burned it
It was the cooking lady
It was the cooking boy
Chloe?
Chloe, I don't want to leave too late.
I don't want us to get stuck in traffic.
Hurry up, please.
Chloe, can you hear me?
Chloe?
Chloe.
We can't leave half an hour late
every morning.
I need time
to drop you off and then...
...I have to go to the garage
and then I have to go to work.
Come on.
You know, I was thinking...
...maybe we should go away
for a weekend together.
What do you think?
A hotel...
...with a view of the sea, a small room.
By the beach.
Enjoy being pampered.
What do you think?
It was just an idea.
I was thinking we should spend
more time together, but it's...
...up to you.
You don't have to.
Wait, I'll be back.
Chloe, don't give me a hard time
this morning, OK?
Do you hear?
Chloe, do you hear me?
No fuss this morning.
I have a difficult case in court.
Dry yourself, get dressed, and let's go.
Alright?
Alright.
Can you please leave?
OK, but hurry up.
Stop.
Who was there that day?
You perhaps? No.
Yes, you've already told me this
dozens of times
and it's always the same.
You tell me the same thing every time!
Princess! Princess! Princess!
Talk! Tell me! Explain!
But that's nonsense.
That's not what happened.
You should have thought
about it before.
Well, yes, she's here.
But that's not how it happened.
We've talked about this.
It's not you, it's me.
Nonsense! You're a joke.
You know this is wrong.
This is nonsense!
What is it now, Chloe?
What's going on?
I can't put up with this every morning.
I have a schedule, too.
I don't want to go.
Listen, every day
I have to deal with schizophrenics,
alcoholics who beat their wives,
thieves who stole scooters,
dealers...
Do you think I want to go?
No, but I go anyway.
You don't understand.
I've had enough.
I can't take it anymore.
You don't know
what I'm going through.
What's going on here?
Tell me.
I'm listening.
It's not going well.
Not going well at all.
That's because you started
in the middle of the year.
Give yourself some time,
and you'll be fine. You'll see.
I'm going through hell.
Aren't you overreacting a little bit?
We've all been there.
You just need time to adjust.
Toughen up a bit and you'll be fine.
Do you want me to talk to Mr. Vallon?
Things will change, you'll see.
I promise it'll be OK.
Come on.
Let's go, because
I'm really gonna be late now.
Come on.
OFFICE
Get out!
Get out! Get out!
Come on, let's go away together.
We'll leave now. We needn't tell anyone.
We won't call the school. Fuck them!
What do you say?
Let's go away together right now.
Let's do it!
And who cares about Jacques?
Fuck him as well!
Fuck them all!
We'll go away together.
I know a little place on a clifftop.
It's beautiful, and...
there is a lighthouse
that guides lost boats at night.
And...
At this time of year it will be quiet,
which will make things easier.
I won't take many clothes,
just one or two things.
At any rate...
We should have done this ages ago.
I'm sorry I've neglected you.
I was too engrossed in my work.
But now we'll make up
for lost time, right?
It's still possible.
I may not have always been there,
but that doesn't mean I don't love you.
I love you with all my heart.
Chloe?
Chloe.
With all my heart.
It doesn't matter about school.
I can teach you.
We'll look up the syllabus
and I'll help you.
You'll never have to go back.
I promise.
No more school.
Where did I put the keys?
Help! Help!
Shut up! No one is coming!
Open the door
or we'll break it down!
Don't think you're all that,
you dirty slut!
You won't escape
through the shithole, so open up!
Stop it. I'll open the door.
Fucking open it, then!
The longer you wait, the worse it gets!
We won't do anything to you,
just beat you up a bit!
Why are you picking on me?
I didn't do anything to you!
You think you're a star,
but we'll bring you down to earth!
It's for your own good.
You'll thank us later.
There's no point talking to her.
She's too stupid to understand.
Open up, bitch!
Alright. I'll open the door.
Come on, get out!
I didn't do anything.
We don't care!
You're not at Mom and Dad's house now.
You are not the queen here.
- But I don't see myself as the queen.
- Prove it, then!
Get down on your knees like a bitch
and kiss our feet!
On your knees!
We're gonna take a few pictures
for the school's Facebook page.
So everyone can see
that you are our slave now.
Please, I'd like to go home.
If you don't kiss her feet,
you'll never see home again!
And give us a smile
or we'll shave your head.
Do you want me to cut
that pretty princess face?
Kiss her feet, then!
I said smile!
Come on! Smile more!
Are you alright?
There were bricks.
Bricks?
Forget it.
You screamed.
You're not having a stroke, are you?
You seem absent. Are you alright?
Yes, sorry.
I was dreaming.
We have to go now.
We are in a hurry.
OK.
Hello, Chloe!
How are you?
Aren't you going to say hello
to your favorite neighbor?
What happened?
She had an accident?
No, no, she's doing fine.
We need to leave now.
We are going on vacation.
On vacation?
In the middle of the school year?
Are you alright?
Yes, I'm good.
You're acting weirdly, Julia.
I swear.
If you have a problem,
if there is anything I can do,
I'm right next door.
I know, Emma.
Well...
have a good holiday, then.
There's something
you're not telling me.
I know her. She's not well.
- We really must...
- Julia, tell me what's going on.
Nothing.
Excuse me! Chloe.
Chloe.
I remember when you were born,
you were so small.
So fragile.
I was sure you wouldn't last the night.
But then you did.
And then another day and another day.
And then I watched you grow up.
And I saw you become strong,
become beautiful.
And then...
...I stopped seeing you.
And I forgot this fragile life
that had come out of me.
But it will all work out.
We need to take some time
for ourselves.
We need to rest.
We'll dress up
and go to the best restaurants.
Eat large platters of seafood.
They say sea air is good for us.
No?
Isn't that what they say?
Answer me, please.
Answer me.
Please.
Please answer me.
Please. Please.
Let go of the wheel!
Let go of the wheel.
Get out!
Come on!
Let go of me!
Come on, calm down.
- I want my daughter!
- Calm down.
I want my daughter!
We've all been there.
I will be your guide.
Please follow me, Nathan.
Where am I?
What do you think?
And you are?
I am nobody.
I accompany souls
to their eternal torment.
Really?
All this is not enough?
We have to endure it forever.
Yeah, sure. Why not.
It depends on your wrongdoing.
But most of the time
it is eternity that awaits you.
You know what I did.
She had an advanced stage
of multiple sclerosis.
It's not murder.
Did she ask you to do it?
No. She was in agony.
It made her lose her mind.
I am not here to judge.
I am only participating
in the execution of the sentence.
Where are my judges?
Who listened to what I had to say?
I loved my wife.
I don't belong here.
This is a mistake!
I want to talk to the person in charge!
There is no one to listen to you.
There is no other place than here.
After death there is only hell.
Humanity is evil by nature
and must atone for its sins.
Follow me, Nathan.
Whatever we do, we are condemned
to suffer here until the end of time?
For most of you, yes.
But here time has no end.
One suffers forever, remembering
with nostalgia one's earthly life.
Great.
So where do we start?
Do I get my balls ripped off,
my eyes gouged out?
Delightful idea, but no.
You will go through the first circle
in semi-isolation
until you forget the memory
you have of your body.
You will become a pure spirit
of pain and despair.
Quite frankly...
...I don't like you.
And I don't like what you're saying.
If you're looking to scare me,
you've succeeded.
- Please.
- After you.
It's protocol.
Really?
No, no, no, no.
That's not gonna be possible.
I'm not going to be able
to take this forever.
It's what we do here.
Make you endure the unbearable
and make sure it never stops.
You'll see, you'll never get used to it.
Is there nothing but despair here?
Nothing for you anyway, I'm afraid.
Well, on that note, let me explain.
You are here in quarantine.
- You will be confined in...
- No, not again!
40 days here? No way!
No, a quarantine here corresponds
to 40 of your centuries,
4,000 years if you prefer.
What do you mean 4,000 years?
You still think like a human.
And, indeed, it can seem long.
But 40 centuries is not much
compared to what awaits you afterwards.
It's ridiculous.
It's completely disproportionate!
- It makes no sense.
- Let me finish.
At the end of your quarantine,
the process of shattering all recollection
of your being will be completed.
You will have no other function
than to suffer.
You are totally mad.
Flattery will get you nowhere.
I will come and get you
at the end of your quarantine.
See you soon, Nathan.
I won't be able to endure this
for 4,000 years. I'm telling you now!
Who's here? What's going on?
Who are you?
Nathan. And you?
Billy. Are you my new toy?
No. I don't think so.
Yes, you are. You look like a toy
so you're my toy.
No, no, I'm not your toy, Billy!
Yes, you are!
OK, don't get mad!
What do you want to play?
I want to beat you up!
Beat me up? No.
Don't you want to play something else?
- No!
- How about I think of someone
and you have to guess who?
Wake up!
What did I do?
We're losing souls
because of you, Billy.
He was not intended for reincarnation.
You let a damned soul
return to an earthly life.
You created an Antichrist!
Tomorrow, your body
will have grown back.
Go and bring him back.
I will find his soul, Norgl,
no matter what his new body is.
I will find him, I promise,
and I will bring him back here.
Sorry. I beg your forgiveness.
Hell has no mercy!